

JULIEN LIABEUF

Business Developer Project Manager

Profile

I am a highly motivated, hard working person. I always relish a challenge, and seize the opportunity to apply my diverse skillset. I am goal oriented and extremely autonomous in my work.

I enjoy learning new things and keep myself in a continuous learning cycle. Technology Watch is part of my daily routine.

My organization techniques and strategic view make me a very productive person. I know how to effectively take a project from beginning to end.

Who I am

I am a 29 year old Frenchman, currently living in Bangkok, who loves travels, food, fencing, technology, science and motorcycles.

While **French** is my native language, I am fluent in **English** and also converse in basic **Thai**.

I enjoy reading about travel, philosophy and science.

Contact me

Phone:

+66(0)87-703-0926

Email:

julien@liabeuf.fr

Website:

https://jlia.co/resume

GitHub:

https://github.com/julien731

Experience

Co-Founder, Business Developer

N2Clic Limited, Hong Kong

2009 - 2016

I have co-founded N2Clic Ltd., a web development agency, where I took care, among other things, of **business development**, **project management** and **PR**. *Managed 5 staff*. *Agerage year-to-year growth 20%*. *High customer satisfaction*.

Co-Founder, Marketing Manager

RueduTheme SAS, Lyon, France

2011 - 2014

I have co-founded RueduTheme, a French marketplace selling website themes. I was in charge of the company's **marketing strategy and execution**.

Online Marketing Manager

Kalistick SAS, Lyon, France

2010 - 2012

As the e-marketing manager at Kalistick (acquired by Coverity), I was in charge of developing our online presence, improving our lead generation and tracking KPIs. I was also involved in planning the global marketing strategy.

Online traffic *274%. Conversion rate *2.15%. Session time *156%.

Business Developer

Acteasy SARL, Pierre-Bénite, France

2008 - 2009

I worked on three primary projects at Acteasy: development of a **new subsidiary**, improvement of **management workflow**, development and **implementation of a CRM**.

Achievements

N2Clic Ltd.

Web Agency - n2clic.com

I successfully ran a **web agency for 7 years**. We created close to one hundred websites and helped dozens of clients. *Read more at http://jlia.co/n2clic*

Awesome Support

Helpdesk Software - getawesomesupport.com

I led the development and promotion of a helpdesk software that **quickly became #1** in its field. I sold the business in 2016 for a 2.7 multiple (above industry average).

Education

Bachelor in Business Management

Lyon 1 University, Lyon, France

2008 - 2009

I graduated "GEA" (stands for the French translation of Management of Businesses and Administrations) with a major in IT Business.

HNC International Trade Relations

La Martinière Duchère, Lyon, France

2006 - 2008

Foundations in international law and world economy. The advanced fields of study are management, transport and logistics. I have completed 3 internships at that time: 2 in France and 1 in London.

A-Level: Math, Physics, Biology

F-J Armorin, Crest, France

2006